Sai Allala

React Developer

Respectful self-motivator gifted at finding reliable solutions for software issues. Knowledgeable on all aspects of Facebook's design best practices and emerging UI development techniques. Experienced in building components and fixing elusive bugs and offering skills in React and JavaScript. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in the financial industry.

Work History

2020-03 -Current

React Developer

Wells Fargo, Charlotte, North Carolina

- Drafted detailed technical documentation for use by collaborating personnel and other developers.
- Maintained existing applications and designed and delivered new components.
- Coordinated with UI-lead to evaluate and improve software development
- Authored code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in future code releases and patches.

2019-08 -2020-03

Full Stack Developer

Collabera, Basking Ridge, New Jersey

- Ushered group of 4 members to develop a web application within one week.
- Presented numerous presentations on Java, Spring,
 MySQL to a group of 20 engineers.
- Published more than 30 technical articles on subjects such as Java, Javascript and SQL and consolidated a single source of information for other colleagues to view and learn.

Education

2015-08 -2019-06

Bachelor of Computer Science

Chaitanya Bharathi Institute Of Technology - Hyderabad, India

Contact

Address

Charlotte, NC, 28269

Phone

(609) 712-7245

E-mail

skrallala752@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/sai-allala

Skills

CSS3, HTML5



JavaScript



React, React Redux, React

Saga



React Testing Library



Jira



Jenkins



UDeploy



Java, Spring Boot, MySQL

